Andrii Babintsev

Ukraine



andrii.babintsev@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/andriibabintsev

Summary

Game developer

Have experience in developing HTML5 + JavaScript ES6 or Typescript games, using Three.js, Phaser 2, Phaser 3, Blacksmith2d.

Strong knowledge of algorithms, patterns, data structures, linear algebra, OOP.

English level: B2 (upper intermediate)

Experience



Middle Game Developer

Borna Technology

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Developed 3D games for web (3-5 months per game)

Mentored junior developers

Estimated time for new projects

Technologies used: JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js, Blacksmith 2d, Cannon.js, Rapier

Junior Game Developer

Borna Technology

Nov 2019 - Sep 2021 (1 year 11 months)

Developed 2D and 3D playable ads (1-2 weeks per game)

Developed 2D games for web (3-5 months per game)

Technologies used: JavaScript, TypeScript, Phaser 3 & 3, Three.js, Blacksmith 2d, Cannon.js, Planck.js

Education



Donetsk National Technical University

Engineer's degree, Automation and control systems

2004 - 2009

Faculty of Computer Information Technologies and Automation

Licenses & Certifications



Node.js developer - Hexlet

Skills

JavaScript • Phaser • Game Development • Node.js • ECMAScript 2015 • Git • Three.js • WebGL